https://www.butterflylife.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode/

My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Search:
Size
Mini (1" - 4")
Small (5" - 7")
Medium (8" - 10")
Large (11" - 15")
X-Large (16" - 18")
Gray
Color Cont.
Size
Mini (1" - 4")
Small (5" - 7")
Medium (8" - 10")
Large (11" - 15")
X-Large (16" - 18")
Gray
Color Cont.
Size
Mini (1" - 4")
Small (5" - 7")
Medium (8" - 10")
Large (11" - 15")
Size
Mini (1" - 4")
Small (5" - 7")
Medium (8" - 10")
Large (11" - 15")
X-Large (16" - 18")
Size
Mini (1" - 4")
Small (5" - 7")
Medium (8" - 10")
Large (11" - 15")
X-Large (16" - 18")
Gray
Color Cont.
Size
Small (5" - 7")
Medium (8" - 10")
Large (11" - 15")
My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Search:
Search
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Loading...
Privacy Policy
Privacy Is Important
Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy sets out how Bugs-n-Blooms uses and protects any information that you give Bugs-n-Blooms when you use this website. Bugs-n-Blooms is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Bugs-n-Blooms may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
SecurityWe take every precaution necessary to protect your private information.  When you enter in your sensitive information via the website, be assured that your information is always protected.  When we collect sensitive information you will see our secure website "https" and information that is collected is sent to us encrypted so your information is never stored.  Transactions on the site are protected with up to 256-bit Secure Sockets Layer encryption. Payments online are processed through Authorize.net and/or Paypal through their secure servers and your information is 100% confidential. Bugs-n-Blooms is a verified vendor with TrustWave which is an indicator of PCI compliance to both you our customers and our credit card processor or bank.
AccountAn account will automatically be created for you when you complete checkout.  To access your account, please make note of your temporary password.  You can log into your account and update your password at anytime.  You can view messages, order status, manage returns, and view wish lists and so much more.  If you forget your password, simply click here and enter your email address and then you can reset your password.
CopyrightAll photos and content on this website are copyrighted and the sole property of the individual photographers and Bugs-n-Blooms, LLC under the Digital Millennium Copyright Act.  Theft of content or photos will be reported.  Please contact us for permission to use any of our photos or content found on this website or affiliated websites owned and published by Bugs-n-Blooms, LLC. All materials, including products and their design details, images, logos, icons, photographs, copy and other materials that appear as part of this web site (collectively, the "Content") are properties owned by Bugs-n-Blooms, LLC and are protected by copyright or other intellectual property laws. The Contents of our web site, the web site as a whole and our product designs may not be reproduced, published, scanned or distributed, in whole or in part, without the expressed written prior permission of Bugs-n-Blooms, LLC.  Copyrights registered under the authority of the United States Copyright Office and may be subject to international protection under the Berne Convention, UCC, TRIPS Agreement, or other international treaties.
TrademarkBugs-n-Blooms® and the Bugs-n-Blooms Logo are registered service marks of Bugs-n-Blooms, LLC and may not be used without permission. Bugs-n-Blooms, butterflylife.com and other associated websites, graphics, logos, and service names in relation to Bugs-n-Blooms, LLC are trademarks of Bugs-n-Blooms. The trademarks of Bugs-n-Blooms may not be used in connection with any product or service that is not of Bugs-n-Blooms, LLC, in any manner that is likely to cause confusion among customers, or in any manner that disparages or discredits Bugs-n-Blooms. All other trademarks not owned by Bugs-n-Blooms, LLC that appear on this site are the property of their respective owners, who may or may not be affiliated with, connected to, or sponsored by Bugs-n-Blooms, LLC.
DisclaimerThis site is provided by Bugs-n-Blooms, LLC on an 'as is' basis. Bugs-n-Blooms, LLC will not be liable for any damages of any kind arising from the use of this site, including, but not limited to direct, indirect, incidental, punitive and consequential damages. Bugs-n-Blooms, LLC reserves the right to make changes to the site, these disclaimers, and the terms and conditions at any time.
What We CollectWe may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What We Do With The Information We GatherWe require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
How We Use CookiesA cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links To Other Websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling Your Personal Information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at customerservice@butterflylife.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to customerservice@butterflylife.com
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List Of Cookies We Collect
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You sesssion ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Magerips Help Us to Keep Magento Healthy - Report All Bugs (ver. 1.9.2.4)
© 2017 Bugs-n-Blooms LLC All Rights Reserved.
Top
Processing...
0 item(s) in your cart
Total item
Cart Subtotal $0.00
Checkout
